singnet.com.sg 2002-12-09

# Welcome to SingNet: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement for SingNet Pte Ltd**

SingNet has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website: http://www.singnet.com.sg

We use your IP address to help increase efficiency, diagnose possible problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site.

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

This site contains links to other sites. SingNet is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys and competitions ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Classified Ads**  
This message board is available to all Netizens. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [ **abuse@singnet.com.sg**](mailto:abuse@singnet.com.sg).
